

## **PROFILE**

I am a motivated Front-End Developer with experience creating custom websites using HTML5, CS3 and JavaScript. I am familiar with Back-End Development using Node JS as well. I possess strong analytical skills with focus on accurate and prompt results.

#### CONTACT

PHONE: 818-281-8253

WEBSITE: Portfolio

EMAIL: Bryan.Ballare@gmail.com

#### **HOBBIES**

Web Design Programming Cars Gaming

# BRYAN BALLARE

Front-End Web Developer

### **EDUCATION**

#### California State University - Northridge

September 2017 – December 2019 Bachelor of Science, Business Marketing GPA: 3.25.

## **UCLA Extension Full Stack Coding Boot Camp**

September 2019 – December 2019 Full Stack development encasing HTML5, CS3, JavaScript, Node JS, React and MySQL.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Mr. Ardi's Catering - Marketing Coordinator, Internship

September 2019 - Current

Creating social media posts to attract new followers, working with the Marketing Director regarding the launch of a new ready-prep meal service and adding a full functioning menu option to the website.

# KT Motoring – Marketing Coordinator, Internship

March 2019 - August 2019

Developed strategies to increase relations with customers which included updating the social media accounts daily and creating events. Increased social media presence reported a weekly growth in customers with 64% being new customers and the remaining 36% being repeat customers.

## **SKILLS**

